Guide to the James Harvey Rogers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Index to Selected Correspondents
  - Balogh, Thomas (1905-)
    - 13 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 February 21 (Box 13)
      - 1935 April 26 (Box 16)
      - 1936 August 11 (Box 19)
      - 1936 September 14 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 13 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 2 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 26 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 2 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 4 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January undated (Box 20)
  - Baruch, Bernard Mannes (1870-). AL (draft) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1934 December 30 (Box 16)
  - Belser, Irvine F.
    - 26 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 July 12 (Box 12)
      - 1934 October 1 (Box 15)
      - 1935 June 26 (Box 16)
      - 1935 September 21 (Box 17)
      - 1935 September 27 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 3 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November 4 (Box 17)
      - 1935 November 25 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 18 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 29 (Box 17)
      - 1936 April 15 (Box 18)
      - 1936 May 7 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 3 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 13 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 16 (Box 19)
      - 1936 September 30 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 26 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 2 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 7 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 27 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 1 (Box 20)
      - 1937 August 26 (Box 21)
      - 1937 November 8 (Box 21)
      - 1938 December 27 (Box 21)
  - Berle, Adolph Augustus (1895-)
    - 13 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 February 7 (Box 11)
      - 1936 February 18 (Box 18)
      - 1936 February 26 (Box 18)
      - 1936 March 13 (Box 18)
      - 1936 April 24 (Box 18)
      - 1936 December 11 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 14 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 4 (Box 20)
      - 1937 October 21 (Box 21)
      - 1938 March 25 (Box 22)
      - 1938 October 28 (Box 23)
      - 1939 March 7 (Box 24)
      - 1939 April 17 (Box 24)
  - Bernays, Edwin L. (1891-)
    - 36 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 November 9 (Box 9)
      - 1932 April 9 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 23 (Box 10)
      - 1932 May 6 (Box 10)
      - 1933 February 3 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 8 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 17 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 21 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 7 (Box 11)
      - 1933 April 17 (Box 11)
      - 1933 July 11 (Box 12)
      - 1933 July 17 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 5 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 6 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October [?] (Box 12)
      - 1933 December 3 (Box 13)
      - 1934 September 14 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 7 (Box 15)
      - 1935 October 1 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 6 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 10 (Box 17)
      - 1936 March 12 (Box 18)
      - 1936 April 10 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 10 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 20 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 6 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 7 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 17 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 10 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 2 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 8 (Box 20)
      - 1938 February 11 (Box 22)
      - 1938 February 25 (Box 22)
      - 1938 April 20 (Box 22)
      - 1938 December 5 (Box 23)
  - Bongiorno, Andrew (1900-)
    - 6 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1934 January 18 (Box 13)
      - 1934 January 24 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 2 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 21 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 27 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 19 (Box 14)
  - Bongiorno, Andrew (1900-)
    - 47 ALS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1922 February 11 (Box 1)
      - 1924 October 3 (Box 2)
      - 1925 March 20 (Box 3)
      - 1925 August 10 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 January 31 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 12 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 6 (Box 3)
      - 1926 June 16 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 5 (Box 3)
      - 1927 January 10 (Box 4)
      - 1927 April 4 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 16 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 10 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 27 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 29 (Box 5)
      - 1928 June 22 (Box 5)
      - 1928 July 22 (Box 5)
      - 1928 September 28 (Box 5)
      - 1928 October 28 (Box 5)
      - 1928 November 25 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 11 (2) (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 16 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 1 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 9 (Box 6)
      - 1929 September 13 (Box 6)
      - 1930 July 22 (Box 7)
      - 1930 November 23 (Box 7)
      - 1931 January 6 (Box 8)
      - 1931 February 8 (Box 8)
      - 1933 May 9 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 11 (Box 12)
      - 1934 January 11 (Box 13)
      - 1934 January 22 (Box 13)
      - 1934 January 28 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 18 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 22 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 24 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 1 (Box 13)
      - 1934 September 26 (Box 15)
      - 1935 January 3 (Box 16)
      - 1935 January 13 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 21 (Box 16)
      - 1935 April 17 (Box 16)
      - 1935 April 19 (Box 16)
      - 1935 May 30 (Box 16)
  - Boyd, George Adams (1898-)
    - 20 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1921 September 19 (Box 1)
      - 1922 October 5 (Box 1)
      - 1922 December 27 (Box 2)
      - 1923 March 19 (Box 2)
      - 1924 April 12 (Box 2)
      - 1926 March 24 (Box 3)
      - [1926-1933] (Box 3–13)
      - 1933 December 20 (Box 13)
      - [1933] (Box 11–13)
      - 1935 January 22 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 16 (Box 16)
      - 1936 January 17 (Box 17)
      - 1936 February 17 (Box 18)
      - 1936 February 20 (Box 18)
      - 1936 February 28 (Box 18)
      - 1936 March 10 (Box 18)
      - 1937 March 8 (Box 20)
      - 1937 December 8 (Box 21)
      - 1938 August 16 (Box 22)
      - 1938 October 30 (Box 23)
  - Bratter, Herbert Max (1900-)
    - 20 ALS, TLS and memos to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 April 10 (Box 14)
      - 1934 April 11 (Box 14)
      - 1934 April 17 (Box 14)
      - 1934 April 18 (Box 14)
      - 1934 April 28 (Box 14)
      - 1934 April 29 (Box 14)
      - 1934 May 3 (Box 14)
      - 1934 May 16 (Box 14)
      - 1934 May 17 (Box 14)
      - 1934 May 24 (Box 14)
      - 1934 May 25 (2) (Box 14)
      - 1934 July 17 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 25 (Box 15)
      - 1934 September 27 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 11 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 14 (Box 15)
      - 1936 February 10 (Box 18)
      - 1936 February 20 (Box 18)
      - 1936 February 28 (Box 18)
      - 1936 October 20 (Box 19)
  - Brown, Harry Gunnison (1880-)
    - 26 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1923 February 16 (Box 2)
      - 1923 May 30 (Box 2)
      - 1923 May 31 (Box 2)
      - 1927 July 18 (Box 4)
      - 1927 July 30 (Box 4)
      - 1930 July 25 (Box 7)
      - 1930 October 4 (Box 7)
      - 1930 October 15 (Box 7)
      - 1931 February 5 (Box 8)
      - 1931 February 17 (Box 8)
      - 1931 March 25 (Box 8)
      - 1931 November 2 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 16 (Box 9)
      - 1931 undated (Box 9)
      - 1932 April 22 (Box 10)
      - 1932 December 7 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 21 (Box 11)
      - 1933 November 23 (Box 13)
      - 1933 December 14 (Box 13)
      - 1935 February 16 (Box 16)
      - 1935 April 16 (Box 16)
      - 1936 January 15 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 21 (Box 17)
      - 1937 May 8 (Box 21)
      - 1939 February 24 (Box 24)
      - 1939 May 2 (Box 24)
  - Bulkley, Robert Johns (1880-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers,, Washington, D.C., 1938 May 9 (Box 24)
  - Burke, Edward Raymond (1880-)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
      - 1938 December 15 (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 10 (Box 24)
  - Burtness, Ogler Burton (1884-)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1923 December 19 (Box 2)
      - 1931 April 1 (Box 8)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Columbia, Mo., 1924 March 29 (Box 2)
  - Bush, Prescott Sheldon (1895-). 2 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1938 February 8 (2) (Box 22)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (1862-1947)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1932 February 9 (Box 10)
      - 1932 December 28 (Box 11)
  - Chandler, Lester Vernon (1905-)
    - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1931 March 24 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 17 (Box 8)
      - 1932 December 20 (Box 11)
      - 1933 August 2 (Box 12)
      - 1933 November 16 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 17 (Box 13)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1934 March 5 (Box 13)
  - Chiang, Mei-ling (Soong) (1897-)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1934 July 25 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 26 (Box 15)
  - Clark, Evans (1888-)
    - 9 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1932 March 25 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 31 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 16 (Box 10)
      - 1932 August 8 (Box 11)
      - 1932 August 12 (Box 11)
      - 1932 August 17 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 21 (Box 11)
      - 1935 February 20 (Box 16)
      - 1935 April 5 (Box 16)
  - Cohrssen, Hans Robert Ludwig (1905-)
    - 40 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1936 May 1 (Box 18)
      - 1936 May 6 (Box 18)
      - 1936 May 23 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 14 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 10 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 11 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 17 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 25 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 5 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 3 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 11 (Box 20)
      - 1937 February 15 (Box 20)
      - 1937 February 19 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 6 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 15 (Box 20)
      - 1937 March 27 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 12 (Box 20)
      - 1937 April 26 (Box 20)
      - 1937 May 7 (Box 21)
      - 1937 May 9 (Box 21)
      - 1937 May 11 (Box 21)
      - 1937 May 25 (Box 21)
      - 1937 June 2 (Box 21)
      - 1937 June 14 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 12 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 15 (Box 21)
      - 1937 July 30 (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 2 (Box 21)
      - 1937 August 26 (Box 21)
      - 1937 September 10 (Box 21)
      - 1937 October 13 (Box 21)
      - 1937 October 25 (Box 21)
      - 1937 December 19 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 24 (Box 22)
      - 1938 February 21 (Box 22)
      - 1938 March 3 (Box 22)
      - 1938 March 9 (Box 22)
      - 1938 June 18 (Box 22)
      - 1938 September 2 (Box 23)
  - Coker, David Robert (1870-1938)
    - 11 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1922 April 17 (Box 1)
      - 1926 May 22 (Box 3)
      - 1928 January 26 (Box 4)
      - 1931 October 17 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 11 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 16 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 20 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 22 (Box 9)
      - 1932 July 23 (Box 11)
      - 1932 December 28 (Box 11)
      - 1936 March 18 (Box 18)
  - Coker, Francis William (1878-1963)
    - 2 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
      - 1930 February 4 (Box 7)
      - 1935 June 12 (Box 16)
  - Commons, John Rogers (1862-1945)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1928 April 17 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 21 (Box 5)
  - Copeland, Morris Albert (1895-)
    - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1926 May 20 (Box 3)
      - 1927 May 31 (Box 4)
      - 1928 April 14 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 3 (Box 5)
      - 1932 December 2 (Box 5)
  - Copland, Douglas Berry (1894-)
    - 10 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1934 January 5 (Box 13)
      - 1936 September 29 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 5 (Box 19)
      - 1936 October 20 (Box 19)
      - 1937 August 19 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 5 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January 12 (Box 22)
      - 1938 January undated (Box 22)
      - 1938 April 27 (Box 22)
      - 1938 December 22 (Box 23)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1934 January 12 (Box 13)
  - Cowles, Alfred (1891-)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 December 20 (Box 13)
  - Cross, Oliver Harlan (1870-)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1931 October 26 (Box 9)
      - 1932 July 6 (Box 10)
      - 1935 November 5 (Box 17)
  - Cross, Wilbur Lucius (1862-1948)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
      - 1922 December 30 (Box 2)
      - 1935 November 7 (Box 17)
  - Cummings, Homer Stillé (1870-1956). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1935 February 27 (Box 16)
  - Davenport, Herbert Joseph (1861-1931)
    - 3 TL and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
      - 1925 undated (Box 3)
      - 1928 March 2 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 9 (Box 5)
    - 6 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1925 May 21 (Box 3)
      - 1925 June 3 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 20 (Box 3)
      - 1927 February 21 (Box 4)
      - 1928 March 5 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 18 (Box 5)
  - Dewey, John (1859-1952). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1931 December 15 (Box 9)
  - Douglas, Paul Howard (1892-). TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1925 June 3 (Box 3)
  - Downey, Sheridan (1884-)
    - 2 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
      - 1939 February 10 (Box 24)
      - 1939 March 8 (Box 24)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1939 February 23 (Box 24)
  - Dunn, James Clement (1890-)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1935 December 5 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 12 (Box 17)
      - 1935 December 30 (Box 17)
  - Early, Stephen Tyree (1889-1951)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 December 14 (Box 13)
      - 1938 September 27 (Box 23)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 December 18 (Box 13)
  - Eccles, Marriner Stoddard (1890-)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 December 6 (Box 21)
    - 6 TL (copies) written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1936 December 12 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 6 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 19 (Box 21)
      - 1937 March 30 (Box 21)
      - 1937 November 23 (Box 21)
      - 1937 December 15 (Box 21)
  - Edie, Lionel Danforth (1893-)
    - 29 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1929 January 18 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 5 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 8 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 29 (Box 6)
      - 1929 October 7 (Box 6)
      - 1931 March 7 (Box 8)
      - 1931 May 22 (Box 8)
      - 1931 June 27 (Box 8)
      - 1931 September 12 (Box 8)
      - 1931 November 2 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 22 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 28 (Box 9)
      - 1932 June 15 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 23 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 29 (Box 10)
      - 1932 August 12 (Box 11)
      - 1932 August 17 (2) (Box 11)
      - 1932 August 24 (Box 11)
      - 1932 November 5 (Box 11)
      - 1933 January 23 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 4 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 21 (Box 11)
      - 1933 undated (Box 11)
      - 1933 April 27 (Box 11)
      - 1933 August 4 (Box 12)
      - 1936 May 22 (Box 18)
      - 1936 June 4 (Box 19)
      - 1939 February 14 (Box 24)
  - Edmiston, Henry H.
    - 6 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1930 February 27 (Box 7)
      - 1933 August 22 (Box 12)
      - 1936 January 16 (Box 17)
      - 1936 August 20 (Box 19)
      - 1937 August 1 (Box 21)
      - 1939 January 16 (Box 23)
  - Ely, Richard Theodore (1854-1943)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1933 February 14 (Box 11)
      - 1933 April 4 (Box 11)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1933 April 14 (Box 11)
  - Farrand, Livingston (1867-1939)
    - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
      - 1923 March 7 (Box 2)
      - 1923 March 24 (Box 2)
      - 1923 June 11 (Box 2)
      - 1925 October 5 (Box 3)
  - Feis, Herbert (1893-)
    - 35 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 January 30 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 6 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 23 (Box 11)
      - 1933 August 25 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 26 (Box 12)
      - 1933 November 7 (Box 13)
      - 1933 December 28 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 21 (Box 14)
      - 1934 December 4 (Box 15)
      - 1934 December 15 (Box 16)
      - 1934 December 20 (Box 16)
      - 1934 December 24 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 4 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 16 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 1 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 4 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 11 (Box 16)
      - 1935 March 15 (Box 16)
      - 1935 April 10 (Box 16)
      - 1935 May 31 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 4 (Box 16)
      - 1935 June 17 (Box 16)
      - 1935 August 22 (Box 17)
      - 1935 October 15 (Box 17)
      - 1936 January 15 (Box 17)
      - 1936 April 4 (Box 18)
      - 1936 July 8 (Box 19)
      - 1936 July 20 (Box 19)
      - 1936 August 3 (Box 19)
      - 1936 November 6 (Box 19)
      - 1937 January 15 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 16 (Box 20)
      - 1937 January 21 (Box 20)
      - 1938 November 1 (Box 23)
      - 1939 February 14 (Box 24)
  - Fish, Hamilton (1888-). Telegram to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1932 October 24 (Box 24)
  - Fisher, Irving (1867-1947)
    - 70 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1915 July 22 (Box 1)
      - 1915 December 18 (Box 1)
      - 1921 July 21 (2) (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 27 (Box 1)
      - 1922 October 26 (Box 1)
      - 1922 December 30 (Box 2)
      - 1924 February 28 (Box 2)
      - 1924 April 5 (Box 2)
      - 1924 July 19 (Box 2)
      - 1925 January 6 (Box 3)
      - 1925 February 10 (Box 3)
      - 1925 March 18 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 6 (Box 3)
      - 1925 June 8 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 19 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 28 (Box 3)
      - 1928 February 8 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 10 (Box 4)
      - 1928 March 12 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 17 (Box 5)
      - 1928 May 1 (Box 5)
      - 1928 July 30 (Box 5)
      - 1929 January 17 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 12 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 15 (Box 6)
      - 1929 April 18 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 10 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 21 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 28 (Box 6)
      - 1929 July 12 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 10 (Box 6)
      - 1930 July 2 (Box 7)
      - 1930 November 29 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 6 (Box 7)
      - 1931 June 13 (Box 8)
      - 1931 July 25 (Box 8)
      - 1931 August 25 (Box 8)
      - 1931 October 3 (Box 9)
      - 1931 October 17 (Box 9)
      - 1931 October 21 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 6 (Box 9)
      - 1931 November 17 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 2 (Box 9)
      - 1931 December 23 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 4 (Box 9)
      - 1932 February 5 (Box 10)
      - 1932 February 11 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 2 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 12 (Box 10)
      - 1932 September 26 (Box 11)
      - 1933 February 6 (Box 11)
      - 1933 December 4 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 20 (Box 14)
      - 1934 March 27 (Box 14)
      - 1934 July 16 (Box 14)
      - 1934 August 1 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 5 (Box 15)
      - 1935 July 2 (Box 16)
      - 1936 February 21 (Box 18)
      - 1936 March 11 (Box 18)
      - 1936 December 9 (Box 20)
      - 1937 August 9 (Box 21)
      - 1938 February 7 (Box 22)
      - 1938 March 26 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 27 (Box 22)
      - 1939 March 7 (Box 24)
      - 1939 March 17 (Box 24)
      - undated (Box 24)
    - 37 ALS, TL copy and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1920 January 14 (Box 1)
      - 1922 May 29 (Box 1)
      - 1924 April 26 (Box 2)
      - 1925 February 6 (Box 3)
      - 1925 February 16 (Box 3)
      - 1925 March 18 (Box 3)
      - 1925 March 26 (Box 3)
      - 1925 June 3 (Box 3)
      - 1925 September 29 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 9 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 14 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October [22-23] (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 20 (Box 3)
      - 1927 September 21 (Box 4)
      - 1928 February 20 (Box 5)
      - 1928 March 9 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 13 (Box 5)
      - 1928 April 27 (Box 5)
      - 1928 September 20 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 8 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 19 (Box 6)
      - 1929 February 22 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 4 (Box 6)
      - 1929 June 4 (Box 6)
      - 1930 January 23 (Box 7)
      - 1930 June 11 (Box 7)
      - 1930 November 12 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 3 (Box 7)
      - 1931 August 21 (Box 8)
      - 1931 August 27 (Box 8)
      - 1931 October 14 (Box 9)
      - 1932 February 10 (Box 10)
      - 1932 March 11 (Box 10)
      - 1932 April 20 (Box 10)
      - 1932 June 4 (Box 10)
      - 1932 October 18 (Box 11)
      - 1933 March 18 (Box 11)
      - 1934 December 1 (Box 15)
      - 1936 December 17 (Box 20)
      - 1938 March 23 (Box 22)
      - 1938 May 28 (Box 22)
      - undated (Box 24)
  - Foster, William Trufant (1879-1950)
    - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place
      - 1924 March 7 (Box 2)
      - 1924 September 3 (Box 2)
  - Frank, Jerome (1889-1957). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1932 December 9 (Box 11)
  - Fraser, Leon (1889-1945)
    - 3 TLS and TL (copy) to James Harvey Rogers, New York
      - 1936 February 7 (Box 18)
      - 1937 July 29 (Box 21)
      - 1938 January 4 (Box 22)
  - Friedrich, Carl Joachim (1901-)
    - 60 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1923 June 23 (Box 2)
      - 1923 July 2 (Box 2)
      - 1923 July 7 (Box 2)
      - 1923 July 12 (Box 2)
      - 1923 August 2 (Box 2)
      - 1923 October 5 (Box 2)
      - 1924 March 5 (Box 2)
      - 1924 August 7 (Box 2)
      - 1924 September 21 (Box 2)
      - 1924 October 29 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 19 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 21 (Box 2)
      - 1924 November 26 (Box 2)
      - 1924 December 26 (Box 2)
      - 1925 January 27 (Box 3)
      - 1925 March 31 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 5 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 20 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 23 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 28 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 30 (Box 3)
      - 1925 July 28 (2) (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 13 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 17 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 18 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 27 (Box 3)
      - 1926 January 9 (Box 3)
      - 1926 January 23 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 11 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 26 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 30 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 15 (Box 3)
      - 1926 April 26 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 5 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 1 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 3 (Box 3)
      - 1926 October 13 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 14 (Box 3)
      - 1926 December 16 (Box 3)
      - 1927 March 22 (Box 4)
      - 1927 July 17 (Box 4)
      - 1927 July 23 (Box 4)
      - 1927 November 6 (Box 4)
      - 1928 September 13 (Box 5)
      - 1929 February 4 (Box 6)
      - 1929 May 2 (Box 6)
      - 1930 May 18 (Box 7)
      - 1930 October 27 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 8 (Box 7)
      - 1930 December 29 (Box 8)
      - 1931 November 1 (Box 9)
      - 1932 January 23 (Box 10)
      - 1933 October 24 (Box 12)
      - 1935 June 3 (Box 16)
      - 1936 April 1 (Box 18)
      - (4) undated (Box 24)
  - Frisch, Ragnar Anton Kittil (1895-)
    - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1930 April 19 (Box 7)
      - 1932 August 20 (Box 11)
      - 1935 October 2 (Box 17)
  - Fry, Charles Luther (1894-)
    - 37 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1924 September 9 (Box 2)
      - 1925 February 25 (Box 3)
      - 1925 April 27 (Box 3)
      - 1925 May 16 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 16 (Box 3)
      - 1925 October 23 (Box 3)
      - 1925 November 30 (Box 3)
      - 1926 February 23 (Box 3)
      - 1926 March 2 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 6 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 14 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 15 (Box 3)
      - 1926 May 29 (Box 3)
      - 1926 November 8 (Box 3)
      - 1928 September 27 (Box 5)